let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A cow?",
    answer: "Moos",
    options: [
      "Bark",
      "Moos",
      "Mews",
      "Quacks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A donkey?",
    answer: "Brays",
    options: [
      "Trumpets",
      "Moos",
      "Brays",
      "Hisses"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A duck?",
    answer: "Quacks",
    options: [
      "Quacks",
      "Whistles",
      "Crows",
      "Sings"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A cat?",
    answer: "Mews",
    options: [
      "Barks",
      "Moos",
      "Mews",
      "Quacks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "An elephant?",
    answer: "Trumpets",
    options: [
      "Brays",
      "Moos",
      "Roars",
      "Trumpets"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A lion?",
    answer: "Roars",
    options: [
      "Laughs",
      "Moos",
      "Roars",
      "Brays"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A dog?",
    answer: "Barks",
    options: [
      "Barks",
      "Moos",
      "Mews",
      "Brays"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A cock?",
    answer: "Crows",
    options: [
      "Quacks",
      "Crows",
      "Hisses",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A lamb?",
    answer: "Bleats",
    options: [
      "Bleats",
      "Bellows",
      "Mews",
      "Howls"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A frog?",
    answer: "Croaks",
    options: [
      "Grunt",
      "Moos",
      "Croaks",
      "Howl"
    ]
  }
];